worldlanguage.com 2001-06-03

# Privacy Policies

| Browsing the Site | Searching | Checkout Explained | Navigation Tips  
---|---|---|---  
About Us | Fax Or Mail Ordering | Sales Guarantee | Packaging  
Privacy Policies | Job Opportunities | Order Tracking | Gift Certificates  
Site Security | Safe Shopping Guarantee  
  
Protecting the privacy of our customers is important to WorldLanguage. In order to keep you fully informed about our use of information we collect at WorldLanguage.com, please read our privacy policy.

**Information We Collect**  
When you order, we ask for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date so that we may process your orders and to notify you of your order status. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop WorldLanguage.com’s design and layout.

**How We Use That Information**  
We currently use the information we collect to fulfill orders. We may use the information to notify you about changes to WorldLanguage’s Web site, our latest services or special offers, or new language products that become available. If you would rather not receive this information, please e-mail us at [unsubscribe@WorldLanguage.com](mailto:unsubscribe@WorldLanguage.com) and ask to be removed from our notification list. When you submit a customer review, we also ask for your e-mail address, although you can choose not to have your e-mail address displayed with your review.

**How We Protect Information**  
WorldLanguage uses a secure server when you place orders or access your account information. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, we protect the customer data we collect against unauthorized access.

**Disclosure Of Information To Third Parties**  
WorldLanguage does not sell, lease or trade personal information with third parties. We may choose to do so in the future with reliable and secure parties, but you can always tell us not to share your information by sending an e-mail to [service@WorldLanguage.com](mailto:service@WorldLanguage.com) and requesting us to never share your personal information.

**Updating Your Information**  
At any time, you may later review or update your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by visiting your online profile area at My WorldLanguage. If you do not have an account, you may also ask to review or update your information by contacting our customer service department at [service@WorldLanguage.com](mailto:service@WorldLanguage.com). To protect the integrity and security of your information, we will also verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Your Consent**  
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by WorldLanguage. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Regardless of later changes, however, we will never use the information you provide under this current notice in a new way without first providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prevent that use. If you have any questions, please contact us at [service@WorldLanguage.com](mailto:service@WorldLanguage.com).

**BBBOnLine Privacy Program**  
WorldLanguage is proud to participate in the Council of Better Business Bureaus’ BBBOnLine Privacy Program and comply with the heightened consumer protections found in BBBOnLine Privacy standards. Further information about this program may be found at [www.bbbonline.org](http://www.bbbonline.org/).
